right day 15 of my videos and day 2 or
day 1 of me talking about myself instead
of my project so today I wanted to talk
about external versus internal just
external like living my life trying to
be better trying to be this version
trying to be more feminine trying to be
a woman trying to be an amazing parent
trying to be all of these things and the
difference when realizing the shift of
doing it from an external force of like
what society says a woman is what
society says a good parent is versus Who
am I Who am I truly and as I say it's a
subtle shift it's actually really not a
subtle shift it's pretty extreme shift
but switching it so that it's not about
looking good for the exterior world it's
not about looking good for to find a
mate to get a job to do all these things
that are external it's about what makes
me feel good what makes me feel
beautiful what makes me feel like I'm
being my most true authentic self and
that's a bad kind of suggestion I'm
still figuring that out I'm still think
of you know what clothes make me feel
good and at the same time totally
getting that I actually don't care and
authentically I don't care what I look
like on 90% most everyday basis I don't
care it's not worth it for me to put in
the hours a day the door okay it's not
hours a day but hours a week for sure to
do what I think society says looks good
I ain't got time for that
so I've got the energy for it it's just
not where I want to be but realizing
that this fu to the world of like I'm
not gonna look good I'm just gonna wear
it's also it's the same as like trying
to look good for them try not to look
good for them and so instead sitting
with myself being quiet and listening to
okay well what what do I actually want
and what is my true authentic self what
does she is she
what does she wear what does she like to
do and a big one for me was my
femaleness my femininity my lack of
femininity and realizing that I do in
fact like women and non-binary people
what does that mean like what does it
because when you are at least for me
when I was heterosexual and there's this
like idea of what a woman is this idea
of what a man is and they match up like
it's like okay so he should be masculine
he should be taller you should be
stronger he should it's not generally
they're not smarter than me but like
that that's what society says that they
you know should be a little older a
little and so then when then I know what
I am because I'm the reverse of that
right that I should be a little shorter
that I should I was never gonna dumb
myself down so being less intelligent
was never a thing but like I should be
more pretty I should spend more time
getting ready than they do I should
spend and then all of a sudden when you
like people of your same gender or
gender that you didn't even really know
existed if you go it's a different
feeling like it's wait am I supposed to
be shorter do I date people that are
older do I do what it's like everything
opens up and you realize well I did I'm
like okay I've lived 36 years of my life
trying to conform to this idea of what a
woman is in order to get a man and yet I
kind of sucked at that and figuring out
what I who I truly am it's still it's an
ongoing journey and figuring out what it
means I mean a lot of I'll do another
video on masculine and feminine this is
more about external external and just
that feeling of Who am I and what's my
authentic self and what's gonna make me
feel beautiful what am i interested in
because I think a lot of interests are
like oh that's not cool or I mean
I've been a geek for a large period of
time so cool maybe it wasn't what I was
trying to do but cool in a geek world
right that maybe then it's not okay to
like sports because then you're your age
and I don't like sports I authentically
don't like sports and but that you're
kind of supposed to fake it and I know
women who legitimately love sports they
are some of the biggest sports fans that
I know and then I know other women who
are like yeah like I'll watch a hockey
game with him like they like in the
beginning in the in the honeymoon stage
they like sports and later on they don't
and I didn't think they liked
consciously or doing that I think that
it's a sub and I know there's areas
where I was like that like the
subconscious like oh well they won't
like me if I'm not that so I should be
that like I should like these things
that everybody likes or I shouldn't like
top 40 music because that's not so cool
and just realizing all the ways that I
was allowing this external world to
dictate what I should like who I should
be who I should like what they should
like and letting that all fall away and
it falls away in stages it's a frigging
onion for sure because you take one
layer away and you've like we've I've
grown up in this world this
heteronormative worlds of masculine men
and feminine women and if you're not
that they're doing something wrong and
realizing that they're that I'm
attracted to I didn't know I was
attracted to that I am Who I didn't know
who I was and it's a fun journey and so
I'm going to be taking you all with me
on that journey because it's still
ongoing and doing more videos on my
personal journey while figuring out how
to explain this global cooperative that
is a big piece of who I am and who I am
has led to it in a very real way and
yeah I know I'm more interested in
people's stories than in when I was
trying to do before like the data and
the how and instead of the why and a big
piece of my why is who I am so today is
day 15 of this hundred video journey
that I'll be on and see if we can get my
first date in these hundred days
the awesome first date with the woman
maybe by a second first kiss with the
woman let's do that all right
okay hope everyone is having a good day
and see you on Monday even though it's a
holiday